(Amy:)Is it going
to be in 3-D?
(Penny:)What? I don't know.
It doesn't matter.
(Amy:)I'm gonna say 3-D.
(Amy:)That'll let her know
the studio has faith in it.
(Leonard:)You're kidding. 3-D?
(Bernadette:)That's what I hear.
(Howard:)Then the studio
must have real faith in it.
Wonder why she
didn't tell me.
(Priya:)Have you been spending time
with your ex-girlfriend?
(Amy:)No...
(Priya:)Then why are you surprised
she didn't tell you?
(Leonard:)Well, it's not as much
"surprised" as
(Sheldon:)you know...
uh... the other thing.
(Priya:)What other thing?
Well, if you... uh...
(Leonard:)I don't... oh...
(Leonard:)What's the word I'm looking for?
(Howard:)I'm not going to help you.
This is hilarious.
(Bernadette:)She's also dating an astronaut.